A Guide to the Withers Family Papers, 1855-1954, Undated
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
- Correspondence 1855-1954, Undated, 158 folders
  - Folder 31. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Personal 1946-1949, 29 items. (Series-folder 1:31)
    Correspondents include: Charles Holland Mortiz, Virginia Terry, Howard A. Noble, Cleaveland J. Campbell, Robert Carter, Robert E. Read, H. Austill Pharr, Vivian H. Umberger, Emily Werkheiser, Dorothy W. DeLong, Bessie Gordon Jones, Mary Kent Withers, Kent Cloyd Withers II, Edwin Royall Carter, Arthur B. Kinsolving II, Ovid M. Johnson, Agnes R. Poage, Richard B. Miller, Virginia Spiller, Elizabeth S. Linthicum, Sue Rector Read, and Elizabeth Hamlett Williams Paxton.
  - Folder 32. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Personal 1950-1952, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:32)
    Correspondents include: Katherine Lord Briggs, Mary Maxwell Gulick, Ovid M. Johnson, Benjamin C. McFadden, Kent Crosby Darling, Elizabeth Hamlett, Helen Gibbons, Jane Radal Hardess, Rose Carter, Rev. Edwin Royall Carter, Janannie McAlpine, Charles O'Ferrall Thompson, Rt. Rev. Charles Clingman, Jim Rea, Elizabeth Otey Williams, William Coalter Paxton, and Ellis M. Frost.
  - Folder 33. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Personal Undated, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:33)
    Correspondents include: Alice Kennon Williams Gravely, Wyatt Massie, Robin Dudley, Mary Turley Goodson Rogers, Emily Alter Werkheiser, Burks Withers Jr., J. M. Peck Jr., Elizabeth Hamlett Williams Paxton, Frederick Crabtree, and Edward Crosby Darling (re: life in pre-Revolution St. Petersburg, Russia).
  - Folder 34. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1899-1928, 5 items. (Series-folder 1:34)
    Correspondents include: J. B. Kingsley, Reginald Fitz Hugh Bigg-Wither, Reeve Chipman of Temple Tours, Fendall Marbury of Massie, Marbury & Bernard Law Firm, and Everett Armstrong Damon of the Storm King School.
  - Folder 35. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1933-1934, 24 items. (Series-folder 1:35)
    Correspondents include: William H. Robinson, Nannie Dean of Wytheville Seventh Day Adventist Church, Willard E. Mead, Joseph Cloyd Kent, Bettie A. Palmer, J. H. Kennon of Pittsburgh Water Bureau, Rt. Rev. Robert Carter Jett of the Episcopal Diocese of Southwest Virginia, Ella McKee, Morris C. Miller of Christiansburg Improvement Corporation, R. W. Massie of Lone Jack Limestone Company, L. M. Johnston, Howard H. McClintic, and Edward N. Lewis of the National Cathedral Association.
  - Folder 36. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1935-1937, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:36)
    Correspondents include: Don D'Ivernois, Rev. W. A. R. Goodwin of Bruton Parish Church, Rev. C. Garmey of Calvary Episcopal Church, F. T. Haigh of Kane Manufacturing Company, Charles M. Thomas of U. S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, John Royall Read of Canadian Westinghouse Company, Gouverneur P. Hance of Saint Barnabas' Free Home, William J. Donaldson of Donaldson and Montgomery, Rev. Clifton Macon of Calvary Episcopal Church, Public Charities Association of Pennsylvania, Carroll H. Fitzhugh of Trinity Cathedral, U. S. Senator Carter Glass, J. N. Camden of Kentucky River Coal Corporation, Willard E. Mead, T. A. Robinson of Calvary Episcopal Church, William S. Thompson Jr. of Calvary Episcopal Church, and Rolfe Sebastian Ewald of S. F. Ewald Insurance Agency.
  - Folder 37. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1938-1939, 23 items. (Series-folder 1:37)
    Correspondents include: J. M. McLaughlin of the Aluminum Company of America, Chester W. Cleaveland of SIgma Chi, Mary Holton Labberton Kirk, Franklin F. Holbrook of the Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania, Rev. Dewall L. Gwathmey of St. John's Episcopal Church, Rt. Rev. Henry St. George Tucker, Bishop of the Episcopal Church, Robert L. Peirce, Dr. Hugh H. Trout, J. A. Anderson of Virginia Military Institute, Rev. Edwin J. Van Etten of Calvary Episcopal Church, Charles E. Kilbourne of Virginia Military Institute, John C. Hagan Jr. of Mason-Hagan Inc., R. W. Massis of Long Jack Limestone Company, and James M. Graham of First National Farmers Bank.
  - Folder 38. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1940-1941, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:38)
    Correspondents include: Rev. Edwin J. Van Etten of Calvary Episcopal Church, James B. Lynch of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, Honorable J. N. Camden of Kentucky, Allen B. williams, Jno. Gibson Jr. and T. A. Robinson of Calvary Episcopal Church, Rev. W. G. Pendleton, Gladys Williams of the Joseph Horne Company, John C. Sheriff of Lindsay, Weis & Hutchinson, Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving II of Calvary Episcopal Church, Robert C. Jett, John Congrove, Dick M. Reeser, A. D. Christian of Christian, Barton & Parker, D. Stewart Templeton, and Edward K. Davis.
  - Folder 39. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1942-1943, 23 items. (Series-folder 1:39)
    Correspondents include: Herbert A. Jacob of Virginia Military Institute, R. S. Marshall of Virginia Military Institute, Campbell Bascom Slemp of the Southwest Virginia Museum, Walter Mitchell, Charles E. Stuart of Stuart, James & Cooke, Inc., S. A. Copp of Carolina Aluminum Company, H. Bartlett Gerrard, Sidney Briggs of North British and Mercantile Insurance Company, George L. Claypool, Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving II of Calvary Episcopal Church, Rev. Donald E. Veale of Calvary Episcopal Church, N. R. High Moor of Trinity Cathedral, Ovid M. Johnson of R. P. Johnson General Machinery.
  - Folder 40. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1944-1945, 29 items. (Series-folder 1:40)
    Correspondents include: Fox Chapel Golf Club, Ovid M. Johnson of R. P. Johnson General Machinery, W. Bedford Moore Jr., W. M. Gifford, James M. Graham of First National Farmers Bank, George S. Topham of First National Farmers Bank, Clayton Torrence of the Virginia Historical Society, Joseph M. Crockett of Crockett and Tutwiler, Rueben A. Lewis Jr. of Finance Magazine, H. J. Derthick of Facing Forward Inc., Arthur M. Scully, John Pomfret of St. John's Episcopal Church, Hugh Thompson Kerr of Shadyside Presbyterian Church, Chester W. Cleaveland of Sigma Chi, and Emma H. Rodgers.
  - Folder 41. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1946, 34 items. (Series-folder 1:41)
    Correspondents include: E. S. Ruffin Jr. of Calvary Episcopal Church, Margaret E. Rich of the Family Society of Allegheny County, Richard E. Phillippi, L. J. Smith of the Aluminum Cooking Utensil Company, Charles E. Kilbourne of Virginia Military Institute, Bishop Austin Pardue, Alexander C. Zabriskie of the Virginia Theological Seminary, Ovid M. Johnson of R. P. Johnson General Machinery, J. W. Cappeau of Richards and Company, Stuart B. Campbell, Robert L. Peirce, General Richard J. Marshall of Virginia Military Institute, Edwin Hodge Jr., A. C. Yorke of Pennsylvania Railroad Company, C. E. Hankla of Wytheville Hotel Company, and W. Coalter Paxton of James L. Miller Tobacco Company.
  - Folder 42. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1947-1948, 17 items. (Series-folder 1:42)
    Correspondents include: H. L. Mitchell of West Penn Power Company, E. A. Jack of Aluminum Company of America, Richard J. Marshall of Virginia Military Institute, Franz Recum, James R. Gilliam Jr. of Lynchburg Trust and Savings, Marion F. Johnson, William Ellis Jones of Jackson Memorial High School in Austinville, Rt. Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving II, Fendall R. Ellis of Wythe County Schools, Robert E. Johnson of Wythe County Chamber of Commerce, Calvary Episcopal Church, Gourveneur P. Hance of St. Barnabas' Free Home, and Austin Pardue of the Episcopal Diocese of Pittsburgh.
  - Folder 43. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1949-1950, 26 items. (Series-folder 1:42)
    Correspondents include: W. F. Halsey of the University of Virginia Development Fund, Rev. Roddey Reid Jr. of St. John's Church in Knoxville, Tennessee, Ernest Garrett, Rev. Sherwood S. Clayton of Grace Episcopal Church of New Orleans, John Huffard, Thomas F. Walker, Charles E. Kilbourne, William S. Thomas of the Diocese of Pittsburgh, Augustus K. Oliver of the Chamber of Commerce of Pittsburgh, H. H. Donaldson of Mercy Hospital, Calvary Episcopal Church, Charles A. Tracy of Amherst Congregational Church in New Hampshire, Richard Milton Sieg, Ann Adams of Kaufman Department Store, Lucius W. Robinson Jr. of Calvary Episcopal Church, Harvey Havelock Smith, Merrill E. Prichard of Sigma Chi, and F. C. Schreiber of Electrical Engineering Consulting.
  - Folder 44. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers - Professional 1951-1952, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:44)
    Correspondents include: Arthur M. Gates Jr. of Wythe County Broadcasting Company, Carleton Barnwell of the Protestant Episcopal Theological Seminary in Virginia, Richard J. Marshall of Virginia Military Institute, Waller Poage, Ralph Munn of the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, Herbert A. Jacob of Virginia Military Institute, O. B. Crosser of Davey Tree Expert Company, A. D. Huddleston of the Aluminum Company of America, E. L. Garrett, H. A. Bryon of the Church Club of Pittsburgh, and George T. Harrell of Bowman Gray School of Medicine.
  - Folder 45. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Virginia Withers Ast 1938-1939, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:45)
  - Folder 46. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Stuart Bland Campbell 1906 - 1952, Undated, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:46)
  - Folder 47. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Bette Darling 1933-1934, Undated, 6 items. (Series-folder 1:47)
  - Folder 48. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Nelle Powell Payne Darling Undated, 7 items. (Series-folder 1:48)
  - Folder 49. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Anne H. Patrick Kent 1911-1938, Undated, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:49)
  - Folder 50. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Charlotte Miller Kent 1933, Undated, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:50)
  - Folder 51. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Charlotte Kent Pinckney 1933, Undated, 18 items. (Series-folder 1:51)
  - Folder 52. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Flora Stuart 1931-1942, Undated, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:52)
  - Folder 53. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - from Mary Cloyd Kent Withers II 1948, Undated, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:53)
  - Folder 54. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1894-1918, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:54)
    Correspondents include: Sue N. Graham, Weningham Lyons Spelman, May Walton Kent, Mary E. Pogue, Edward Crosby Darling, Florence A. Smith, Margaret B. Brown, and Jack Burress.
  - Folder 55. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1924-1929, 8 items. (Series-folder 1:55)
    Correspondents include: M. W. Talbot, Emily W. Fleming, Elise Caake Ward, B. S. Miller, Helen T. Wiekman, and Tyler Gatewood Kent.
  - Folder 56. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1924-1929, 17 items. (Series-folder 1:56)
    Correspondents include: Campbell P. Waugh, Phoebe Kent, Mary Thornhill Williams, Tyler Gatewood Kent, Tom Richardson, Kate T. McClay, Melesse Kerr Alter, Paul Maye, Rhea Davis, Janet Carter Ambler, Nellie Watts Fleming, Robert C. Jett, Arthur C. Thomson, Sally S. Raedhthour, Elizabeth Hamlett Paxton, and Rev. Devall L. Gwathmey.
  - Folder 57. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1933-1945, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:57)
    Correspondents include: Mary B. J. Rodman, Daisy B. Turner, Edwin Royall Carter, Rev. Arthur C. Thomson, S. B. Davis, Elizabeth Edson Butt, Marguerite Fickes, Agnes T. Davis, Kate T. McClay, Kittie Filler, Lucy M. Cloyd, Phoebe Kent Scholl, Mrs. W. T. Moore, Ellen M. Gayle, Carrie Royall Thomas, and Mrs. Kenneth McAlpine.
  - Folder 58. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1936-1937, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:58)
    Correspondents include: Joseph Cloyd Kent, George J. Alcorn and Company, Lucile Donaldson, Phoebe Kent Scholl, Robert Craig Kent Jr., Ishie Halpin, Colonial Art Furniture Company, Emily K. Crockett, and Mary Agnes Repass.
  - Folder 59. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1938-1939, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:59)
    Correspondents include: C. Thurman Scott, Fannie Hounshell, Sue R. Waugh, Emily T. Watterson, Ishie Halpin, Sara Kent Oswald, Kent Crosby Darling, Virginia P. Brown, Sue Peyton, May Kent Repass, Marguerite Webb Fickes, Louisa S. Sinclair, Annabell C. Secombe, Sue A. Rogers, Joseph E. Caldwell re: mental illness of Robert Craig Kent Jr., and Elizabeth Waller Wilkins.
  - Folder 60. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1940-1941, 23 items. (Series-folder 1:60)
    Correspondents include: Olin Rogers, Sue Nelson Rogers, Mete Goodson, Sue Peyton Broun, Mary Goodson Rogers, Louisa S. Sinclair, Jane Hardess, Agnes Poage, Eliza B. Haskins, Mada Winters, Margaret Scott Caroline Sanders, Percy Blair, Hughes Clark, Frances E. Lacy, and J. J. Demskie.
  - Folder 61. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1942-1943, 18 items. (Series-folder 1:61)
    Correspondents include: Ann Patrick Kent Jacobsen, Richard R. Beasley, Elizabeth J. Jaeger, Amy Caldwell, William Watson Smith, Genevieve B. Alexander, Kent Crosby Darling, Lillian M. Simmons, Octavia V. Morrow, Frani B. Muser, Marguerite Webb Fickes, Mary M. Restelli, Annabell C. Secombe, Mary Breckinridge of Frontier Nursing Service, Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving, and Richard Sieg.
  - Folder 62. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1944-1946, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:62)
    Correspondents include: Sue Peyton Kent Broun, Ishie Halpin, Ida W. Pereney, Julian S. Gravely, Towns Bremer, Jacob McGavock Boyd, Mary Breckinridge of Frontier Nursing Service, Jane Hardess, Octavia V. Morrow, G. S. Topham, W. D. Pollard, and Phoebe Kent Scholl.
  - Folder 63. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1947-1949, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:63)
    Correspondents include: Helen H. Church, Mary Breckinridge of Frontier Nursing Service, Mary D. Rowles, Caroline Sanders, Rev. William Lumpkin, Alice Bravely, Josephine Putney Dame, Robert Edwin Withers III, and Jennie McAlpine.
  - Folder 64. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1950-1951, 16 items. (Series-folder 1:64)
    Correspondents include: Josephine Putney Dame, Sallie Read, Janet McGavock Boyd, Margaret Scott, Janet Anderson, Jane Hardess, Marguerite Webb Fickes, Genevieve B. Alexander, Mete Goodson, Elizabeth Otey Williams, Walter J. Rome, Jennie McAlpine, Sam R. Sayers, and Mary Agnes Repass, Morgan.
  - Folder 65. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1952-1953, 7 items. (Series-folder 1:65)
    Correspondents include: J. Nelson, Jennie McAlpine, Kent Crosby Darling, Helen Becker, Laura M. Scoville, William T. Trevillian, and Genevieve B. Alexander.
  - Folder 66. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - Undated B - M Undated, 37 items. (Series-folder 1:66)
    Correspondents include: Mary MacLeod B., Elise Heatherington Beall, Jennet Ann Withers Cook Boyd, Mary Cameron, Mary M. Campbell, Maude Leeves Cooper, S. Curran, Jane Darling, Kenny Darling, Pete Darling, Marjorie Doeller, Jean Hay Ewing, Helen A. Graves, Katherine Hancock, Kitty Smith Hancock, Mary C. Johnson, Lucile Donaldson Kennerly, Mildred Laporte, Minnie McCarter, Katharine McCormick regarding her trip to Soviet Russia, Winifred S. Miller, Octavia Murrow, and Frani B. Muser.
  - Folder 67. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers - Undated, N-W Undated, 23 items. (Series-foder 1:67)
    Correspondents include: Virginia Oswald, May O'Toole, Olive Repass Pope, Mary Goodson Rogers, Dorothy Chandler Rayburn, Margaret Scott, Mary Sumner, Mary Terry, Carrie Thomas, Mary Terry Thompson, Jane Gray Kent Titus, Richard B. Tucker, Sue R. Waugh, Emily Alter Werkheiser, Mary Phillips Whiting, and Rose H. Worthington.
  - Folder 68. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1909-1912, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:68)
  - Folder 69. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1913-1927, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:69)
  - Folder 70. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1928-1952, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:70)
  - Folder 71. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1909-1910, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:71)
  - Folder 72. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1911-1913, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:72)
  - Folder 73. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Kent Cloyd Withers 1914-1915, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:73)
  - Folder 74. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1916, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:74)
  - Folder 75. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1917-1919, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:75)
  - Folder 76. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1922-1929, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:76)
  - Folder 77. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1931-1934, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:77)
  - Folder 78. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1935-1938, 8 items. (Series-folder 1:78)
  - Folder 79. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1940-1951, 16 items. (Series-folder 1:79)
  - Folder 80. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1918-1926, 19 items. (Series-folder 1:80)
    Correspondents include: Maj. Gen. George Barnett, Samuel J. Graham, Robert Edwin Withers R., Edward K. Price, Ralph D. Rinehart, Raymond Hoblitzell, B. B. Boss, William Page Dame, Fritz Grabner, and Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving.
  - Folder 81. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1927-1933, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:81)
    Correspondents include: Eleanor S. Chapman, Charlie Alison Curry, William J. Newton, Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Walter R. Nathan, Wallace Motor Company, Kent Cloyd Withers, Josephine Withers Read, and Georgia Proctor.
  - Folder 82. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. Undated, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:82)
    Correspondents include: Katharine Hancock, Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling, Willie B. Grabner, Kent Crosby Darling, Kent Cloyd Withers, and Mary Cloyd Kent Withers.
  - Folder 83. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1933-1951, Undated, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:83)
  - Folder 84. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1933-1944, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:84)
  - Folder 85. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:85)
  - Folder 86. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:86)
  - Folder 87. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 23 items. (Series-folder 1:87)
  - Folder 88. Correspondence - Frances Haskins Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 25 items. (Series-folder 1:88)
  - Folder 89. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1928- 1929, 17 items. (Series-folder 1:89)
  - Folder 90. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1930-1934, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:90)
  - Folder 91. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. 1928-1949, Undated, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:91)
  - Folder 92. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers to Kent Cloyd Withers Undated, 4 items. (Series-folder 1:92)
  - Folder 93. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1931-1939, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:93)
  - Folder 94. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:94)
  - Folder 95. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. and Frances Haskins Withers to Kent Cloyd Withers 1911-1933, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:95)
  - Folder 96. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Peggy Dewhurst 1928-1929, Undated, 22 items. (Series-folder 1:96)
  - Folder 97. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Betty Murdoch Undated, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:97)
  - Folder 98. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Oliver Scaife III 1928-1934, Undated, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:98)
  - Folder 99. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers from Mary Terry Thompson Undated, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:99)
  - Folder 100. Correspondence - Kent Cloyd Withers - Miscellaneous 1928-1934, 24 items. (Series-folder 1:100)
    Correspondents include: Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Harry F. Marks, Priscilla Guthrie, William H. Rapp, Hugh Rodman, Edwin Van Etten, Edwin Royall Carter, James M. Coleman, and Andy Kirkbacker.
  - Folder 101. Kent Cloyd Withers - Miscellaneous by Surname Undated, 24 items. (Series-folder 1:101)
    Correspondents include: Nancy Allderdice, Virginia Bachman, Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling, Sallie Gibson, Dorothy Glover, Mary S. Gordon, Harriet Gere Jayne, Harriet Marie Jolley, Charlotte Miller Kent, William H. Rapp, Hugh Rodman, Gretchen Rose, and Alice R. Tucker.
  - Folder 102. Correspondence - Miscellaneous by First Name Undated, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:102)
  - Folder 103. Correspondence - Martha Anne Rogers Withers to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. and Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1939-1951, Undated, 29 items. (Series-folder 1:103)
  - Folder 104. Correspondence - Martha Anne Rogers Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1939-1945, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:104)
  - Folder 105. Correspondence - Martha Anne Rogers Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 23 items. (Series-folder 1:105)
  - Folder 106. Correspondence - Martha Anne Rogers Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 22 items. (Series-folder 1:106)
  - Folder 107. Correspondence - Josephine Withers Read to/from Edwin Withers Sr. 1910-1948, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:107)
  - Folder 108. Correspondence - Josephine Withers Read to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. Undated, 6 items. (Series-folder 1:108)
  - Folder 109. Correspondence - Josephine Withers Read to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1924-1941, Undated, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:109)
  - Folder 110. Correspondence - Stephen Putney to Betty Ellison Withers Putney 1878, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:110)
  - Folder 111. Correspondence - Stephen Putney to Betty Ellison Withers Putney 1879, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:111)
  - Folder 112. Correspondence - Stephen Putney to Betty Ellison Withers Putney 1880, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:112)
  - Folder 113. Correspondence - Stephen Putney to Betty Ellison Withers Putney 1881-1882, 8 items. (Series-folder 1:113)
  - Folder 114. Correspondence - Stephen Putney to Betty Ellison Putney Undated, 16 items. (Series-folder 1:114)
  - Folder 115. Correspondence - Stephen Putney - Miscellaneous 1880, Undated, 6 items. (Series-folder 1:115)
    Correspondents include: Charles Duffman and Company, R. E. Hatcher, Josephine Putney Dame, and Mary Virginia Royall Withers.
  - Folder 116. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney to Stephen Putney 1878-1880, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:116)
  - Folder 117. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney from Josephine Putney Dame 1902-1905, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:117)
  - Folder 118. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney from Josephine Putney Dame Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:118)
  - Folder 119. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney from Josephine Putney Dame Undated, 16 items. (Series-folder 1:119)
  - Folder 120. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous 1878-1880, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:120)
    Correspondents include: Janet Anne Withers Cook, H. Coolidge, Susan Dabney Withers Massie, Josephine Withers REad, Kate Massie Smith, and J. D. Jeffries.
  - Folder 121. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous 1881 - 29 October 1905, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:121)